<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Knowledge on</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/</link><description>Recent content in Knowledge on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Testssl</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/testssl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/testssl/</guid><description>Description # testssl.sh is a free command line tool which checks a server&amp;rsquo;s service on any port for the support of TLS/SSL ciphers, protocols as well as some cryptographic flaws.
install # brew install testssl website # https://testssl.sh
sample usage # testssl.sh example.com help # TESTSSL(1) General Commands Manual TESTSSL(1) NAME testssl NAME testssl -- check encryption of SSL/TLS servers SYNOPSIS testssl [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;URI&amp;gt;, testssl [OPTIONS] --file &amp;lt;FILE&amp;gt; or testssl [BANNER OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION testssl is a free command line tool which checks a server's service on any port for the support of TLS/SSL ciphers, protocols as well as cryptographic flaws and much more.</description></item><item><title>Zmap</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/zmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/zmap/</guid><description>ZMap is a fast single-packet network scanner optimized for Internet-wide network surveys. On a computer with a gigabit connection, ZMap can scan the entire public IPv4 address space on a single port in under 45 minutes. With a 10gigE connection and PF_RING, ZMap can scan the IPv4 address space in 5 minutes.
brew install # brew install zmap sample usage # sudo zmap -p 22 69.52.0.0/16 -o output.app sample output # 69.</description></item><item><title>Smap</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/smap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/smap/</guid><description>Description # smap is a fast and multi-purpose subdomain enumeration tool. It supports multiple sources, user supplied resolvers, DNS wildcard filtering like shuffledns etc.
install # brew install smap sample usage # smap 69.52.32.195 sample output # Starting Nmap 9.99 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2023-02-14 23:28 CET Nmap scan report for filetransfer.blackrock.com (69.52.32.195) Host is up. PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 21/tcp open ftp? 22/tcp open ssh? 80/tcp open http? 443/tcp open https?</description></item><item><title>Tcpdump</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/tcpdump/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/tcpdump/</guid><description>tcpdump # description # tcpdump is a tool for capturing and displaying network traffic. It is written in C and uses libpcap for packet capture. It is available for Windows, Linux and Mac OS X. It is licensed under the BSD license.
install # brew install tcpdump help # TCPDUMP(8) System Manager's Manual TCPDUMP(8) NAME tcpdump - dump traffic on a network SYNOPSIS tcpdump [ -AbdDefhHIJKlLnNOpqStuUvxX# ] [ -B buffer_size ] [ -c count ] [ --count ] [ -C file_size ] [ -E spi@ipaddr algo:secret,.</description></item><item><title>Tcpflow</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/tcpflow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/tcpflow/</guid><description>Description # tcpflow is a tool for capturing network data and saving it to files based on the TCP stream. It is useful for capturing network traffic for later analysis, such as with Wireshark.
Download # brew install tcpflow Usage # tcpflow -i en0 -c -C -p -g -B -r 1000000 -l /tmp/tcpflow Options # -i - interface to listen on -c - capture data -C - capture data and print to stdout -p - print packet headers -g - print packet headers and data -B - print packet headers and data in hex -r - set the read buffer size -l - set the directory to save files to References # https://github.</description></item><item><title>Termshark</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/termshark/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/termshark/</guid><description>Description # Termshark is a terminal UI for tshark, inspired by Wireshark.
Installation # brew install termshark Usage # Capture ping packets on interface eth0:
termshark -i en0 Inspect a local pcap:
termshark -r test.pcap Resources # User Guide help # termshark v2.4.0 A wireshark-inspired terminal user interface for tshark. Analyze network traffic interactively from your terminal. See https://termshark.io for more information. Usage: termshark [FilterOrPcap] Application Options: -i=&amp;lt;interfaces&amp;gt; Interface(s) to read.</description></item><item><title>Nmap</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/nmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/nmap/</guid><description>Description # Nmap is a free and open source utility for network discovery and security auditing. Many systems and network administrators also find it useful for tasks such as network inventory, managing service upgrade schedules, and monitoring host or service uptime.
Installation # brew install nmap Usage # nmap -sP 192.168.0.1/24 References # Nmap Nmap - Wikipedia help # NMAP(1) Nmap Reference Guide NMAP(1) NAME nmap - Network exploration tool and security / port scanner SYNOPSIS nmap [Scan Type.</description></item><item><title>Nuclei</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/nuclei/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/nuclei/</guid><description>Description # Nuclei is a fast tool for configurable targeted scanning based on templates offering massive extensibility and ease of use.
Installation # brew install nuclei Usage # nuclei -u https://example.com Resources # Nuclei Getting Started Nuclei Templates Guide Nuclei Templates help # Nuclei is a fast, template based vulnerability scanner focusing on extensive configurability, massive extensibility and ease of use. Usage: nuclei [flags] Flags: TARGET: -u, -target string[] target URLs/hosts to scan -l, -list string path to file containing a list of target URLs/hosts to scan (one per line) -resume string resume scan using resume.</description></item><item><title>P0f</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/p0f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/p0f/</guid><description>Description # What&amp;rsquo;s this? P0f is a tool that utilizes an array of sophisticated, purely passive traffic fingerprinting mechanisms to identify the players behind any incidental TCP/IP communications (often as little as a single normal SYN) without interfering in any way. Version 3 is a complete rewrite of the original codebase, incorporating a significant number of improvements to network-level fingerprinting, and introducing the ability to reason about application-level payloads (e.g., HTTP).</description></item><item><title>Rustscan</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/rustscan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/know/rustscan/</guid><description>Description # RustScan is a modern port scanner written in Rust. It is designed to be fast and easy to use. I
install # brew install rustscan Usage # rustscan - References # Wiki GitHub See also # nmap masscan p0f help # rustscan 2.1.1 Fast Port Scanner built in Rust. WARNING Do not use this program against sensitive infrastructure since the specified server may not be able to handle this many socket connections at once.</description></item></channel></rss>