<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Attack on</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/</link><description>Recent content in Attack on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sqlmap</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/sqlmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/sqlmap/</guid><description>Description # sqlmap is an open source penetration testing tool that automates the process of detecting and exploiting SQL injection flaws and taking over of database servers.
Installation # brew install sqlmap Usage # sqlmap -u &amp;quot;http://example.com/vuln.php?id=1&amp;quot; --dbs Resources # User Guide sqlmap cheatsheet sqlmap cheatsheet help # ___ __H__ ___ ___[&amp;quot;]_____ ___ ___ {1.7.2.3#dev} |_ -| . [,] | .'| . | |___|_ [&amp;quot;]_|_|_|__,| _| |_|V... |_| https://sqlmap.org Usage: python3 sqlmap.</description></item><item><title>Xh</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/xh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/xh/</guid><description>Description # xh is a command-line HTTP client. It is a wrapper around the [reqwest](
Installation # brew install xh Examples # GET # xh https://httpbin.org/get POST # xh POST https://httpbin.org/post &amp;lt; file.json POST with JSON # xh POST https://httpbin.org/post &amp;lt; file.json POST with form data # xh POST https://httpbin.org/post foo=bar baz=quux POST with form data and JSON # xh POST https://httpbin.org/post foo=bar baz=quux &amp;lt; file.json POST with form data and JSON, and a header # xh POST https://httpbin.</description></item><item><title>Ettercap</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/ettercap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/ettercap/</guid><description>Description # Ettercap is a comprehensive suite for man in the middle attacks. It features sniffing of live connections, content filtering on the fly and many other interesting tricks. It supports active and passive dissection of many protocols and includes many features for network and host analysis.
Install # brew install ettercap Sample Usage # ettercap -T -i en0 -M arp:remote / website # https://www.ettercap-project.org
help # ettercap 0.8.3.1 copyright 2001-2020 Ettercap Development Team Usage: ettercap [OPTIONS] [TARGET1] [TARGET2] TARGET is in the format MAC/IP/IPv6/PORTs (see the man for further detail) Sniffing and Attack options: -M, --mitm &amp;lt;METHOD:ARGS&amp;gt; perform a mitm attack -o, --only-mitm don't sniff, only perform the mitm attack -b, --broadcast sniff packets destined to broadcast -B, --bridge &amp;lt;IFACE&amp;gt; use bridged sniff (needs 2 ifaces) -p, --nopromisc do not put the iface in promisc mode -S, --nosslmitm do not forge SSL certificates -u, --unoffensive do not forward packets -r, --read &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; read data from pcapfile &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; -f, --pcapfilter &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; set the pcap filter &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; -R, --reversed use reversed TARGET matching -t, --proto &amp;lt;proto&amp;gt; sniff only this proto (default is all) --certificate &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; certificate file to use for SSL MiTM --private-key &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; private key file to use for SSL MiTM User Interface Type: -T, --text use text only GUI -q, --quiet do not display packet contents -s, --script &amp;lt;CMD&amp;gt; issue these commands to the GUI -C, --curses use curses GUI -D, --daemon daemonize ettercap (no GUI) -G, --gtk use GTK+ GUI Logging options: -w, --write &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; write sniffed data to pcapfile &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; -L, --log &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; log all the traffic to this &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; -l, --log-info &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; log only passive infos to this &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; -m, --log-msg &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; log all the messages to this &amp;lt;logfile&amp;gt; -c, --compress use gzip compression on log files Visualization options: -d, --dns resolves ip addresses into hostnames -V, --visual &amp;lt;format&amp;gt; set the visualization format -e, --regex &amp;lt;regex&amp;gt; visualize only packets matching this regex -E, --ext-headers print extended header for every pck -Q, --superquiet do not display user and password General options: -i, --iface &amp;lt;iface&amp;gt; use this network interface -I, --liface show all the network interfaces -Y, --secondary &amp;lt;ifaces&amp;gt; list of secondary network interfaces -n, --netmask &amp;lt;netmask&amp;gt; force this &amp;lt;netmask&amp;gt; on iface -A, --address &amp;lt;address&amp;gt; force this local &amp;lt;address&amp;gt; on iface -P, --plugin &amp;lt;plugin&amp;gt; launch this &amp;lt;plugin&amp;gt; - multiple occurance allowed --plugin-list &amp;lt;plugin1&amp;gt;,[&amp;lt;plugin2&amp;gt;,.</description></item><item><title>Hashcat</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/hashcat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/hashcat/</guid><description>Description # hashcat is the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest and most advanced password recovery utility, supporting five unique modes of attack for over 200 highly-optimized hashing algorithms. hashcat currently supports CPUs, GPUs, and other hardware accelerators on Linux, Windows, and OSX, and has facilities to help enable distributed password cracking.
Installation # brew install hashcat Usage # hashcat -m 0 -a 0 hash.txt /usr/share/wordlists/rockyou.txt Resources # hashcat hashcat on GitHub See Also # John the Ripper Hydra Ncrack help # hashcat (v6.</description></item><item><title>Hydra</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/hydra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/hydra/</guid><description>Description # Hydra is a fast network logon cracker which support many different services.
Install # brew install hydra Sample Usage # hydra -l root -P /usr/share/wordlists/rockyou.txt ssh:// website # https://github.com/vanhauser-thc/thc-hydra
help # HYDRA(1) General Commands Manual HYDRA(1) NAME hydra - a very fast network logon cracker which supports many different services SYNOPSIS hydra [[[-l LOGIN|-L FILE] [-p PASS|-P FILE|-x OPT -y]] | [-C FILE]] [-e nsr] [-u] [-f|-F] [-M FILE] [-o FILE] [-b FORMAT] [-t TASKS] [-T TASKS] [-w TIME] [-W TIME] [-m OPTIONS] [-s PORT] [-c TIME] [-S] [-O] [-4|6] [-I] [-vV] [-d] server service [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Hydra is a parallelized login cracker which supports numerous protocols to attack.</description></item><item><title>John</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/john/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/john/</guid><description>Description # John the Ripper is a fast password cracker, currently available for many flavors of Unix, Windows, DOS, BeOS, and OpenVMS. Its primary purpose is to detect weak Unix passwords. Besides several crypt(3) password hash types most commonly found on various Unix flavors, supported out of the box are Windows LM hashes, plus lots of other hashes and ciphers in the community-enhanced version.
install # brew install john sample usage # john --wordlist=/usr/share/wordlists/rockyou.</description></item><item><title>Metasploit</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/metasploit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/metasploit/</guid><description>Description # Metasploit is a penetration testing framework that allows you to find and exploit vulnerabilities.
Installation # brew install metasploit Usage # msfconsole Resources # Metasploit Metasploit Unleashed help #</description></item><item><title>Mitmproxy</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/mitmproxy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/mitmproxy/</guid><description>Description # mitmproxy is an interactive TLS-capable intercepting HTTP proxy for penetration testers and software developers.
Installation # brew install mitmproxy Usage # mitmproxy Resources # Features User Guide GitHub help # usage: mitmproxy [options] options: -h, --help show this help message and exit --version show version number and exit --options Show all options and their default values --commands Show all commands and their signatures --set option[=value] Set an option. When the value is omitted, booleans are set to true, strings and integers are set to None (if permitted), and sequences are emptied.</description></item><item><title>Ncrack</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/ncrack/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/ncrack/</guid><description>Description # Ncrack is a high-speed network authentication cracking tool. It can crack more protocols than any other tool of its kind, and is designed to be flexible and highly customizable.
Install # brew install ncrack Sample Usage # ncrack -vv -p 22 -U /usr/share/wordlists/rockyou.txt -P /usr/share/wordlists/rockyou.txt website # https://nmap.org/ncrack/
help # NCRACK(1) Ncrack Reference Guide NCRACK(1) NAME ncrack - Network authentication cracking tool SYNOPSIS ncrack [Options] {target specification} DESCRIPTION Ncrack is an open source tool for network authentication cracking.</description></item><item><title>Socat</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/socat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:49:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/attack/socat/</guid><description>Description # socat is a command line based utility that establishes two bidirectional byte streams and transfers data between them.
install # brew install socat website # http://www.dest-unreach.org/socat/
help # socat(1) socat(1) NAME socat - Multipurpose relay (SOcket CAT) SYNOPSIS socat [options] &amp;lt;address&amp;gt; &amp;lt;address&amp;gt; socat -V socat -h[h[h]] | -?[?[?]] filan procan DESCRIPTION Socat is a command line based utility that establishes two bidirectional byte streams and transfers data between them.</description></item></channel></rss>