<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tools on</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/</link><description>Recent content in Tools on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python &amp; Neovim</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/python-neovim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 19:37:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/python-neovim/</guid><description>language &amp;amp; text editor
What do you need to have? # Hej, today we begin learning with Nutek to be able to use it how I see it fit. First be sure you have one of the following:
neosb/nutek-core:0.4.0 from Docker Hub Nutek from crates.io or Github - working on a fix You could follow on with Python3, pip, venv and Neovim What you will learn? # I want to show you few Python use cases and how to write code in Neovim.</description></item><item><title>Python3. Filling the Tank</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/python3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 14:28:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/python3/</guid><description>⛽️ for our rocket 🚀
Ground-up # In previous post I tried to show you how to write simple program in neovim and run using python3. Today I want to fill in the gaps in your knowledge of my understanding of how developer work. First of all we will touch on some Vim commands that migh be useful and then we&amp;rsquo;ll build a tool that show where International Space Station is and who is currently in space.</description></item><item><title>Hugo. My First Website</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/hugo/</guid><description>Create YOUR first website # Hej!
This New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve you have so many new resolutions that you need to get them into one place, and make them public, so you can be as transparent as your nearest politician is.
So you heard that there is GitHub, Nutek, Szymon, Hugo and whoever I have to mention to make you test this, because it&amp;rsquo;s so awesome to have your own static website build with Hugo Markdown and all crazy stuff.</description></item><item><title>Bing Search</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/bing-search/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 07:17:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tools/bing-search/</guid><description>and explore 🌍
Using bing-search you can find information that you want. Although limited to displaying only headers, just like on the graphical interface during initial look up, it might help you tackle your problems better.
Combined with w3m - terminal web browser you can practically not miss the needle in a haystack, and equiped with proper knowledge of search queries syntax, you can achieve magic ✨!
Basics # Simple usage can&amp;rsquo;t be simpler:</description></item></channel></rss>